adsy.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Adsy

_Updated May, 2018_

On 25 May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the existing 1995 EU Data Protection Directive (European Directive 95/46/EC). Adsy is committed to GDPR compliance across the company, and we have evaluated the new requirements and restrictions imposed by the GDPR as well as have reviewed where and how we collect, use, store and dispose of personal data and updating policies, standards and documentation as necessary.

In circumstances where we ask you to provide any kind of personal information in order to use any of our websites or services, all such information will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

The following Privacy Policy is a reviewed version dated by May, 2018 that complies with the Regulation.

### BY USING THE SERVICE, YOU CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

At Adsy.com, we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information that we may receive from you and other users of the Adsy.com service, through our software, mobile applications and our website located at adsy.com (the “Website”). Such service, the software, mobile applications and the Website are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “Service”. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service.

Adsy.com reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Website at http://adsy.com/privacy-policy/. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Service will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

## 1\. WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

1.1. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Adsy.com collects non-personally identifiable information that your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes your Internet connection and hardware specs, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

1.2. Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, we collect your personal information such as your full name, credit card information, billing address, your email address, your Skype ID, history of communication with Adsy.com, history of payments, IP address, system information, your activities on the Website, and any other information you provide when using Adsy services or interacting with us in any way.

We do not collect your sensitive personal information, in particular, confidential medical facts, racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs or sexuality.

If we hold any information about you which is incorrect or if there are any changes to your details or if you wish to see a copy of the information that we hold about you, please let us know at contact@adsy.com so that we can keep our records accurate and up to date. You are also free to contact us regarding deletion of some or of all information we have gathered about you as well as your Adsy account.

1.3. Additionally and only upon your grant of respective permissions we may collect information from third party service providers.

Our Data Protection Officer monitors relevancy of the information collected as well as compliance with the GDPR and performs all the tasks determined by Art. 39 of GDPR. You can contact our Data Protection Officer regarding privacy questions related to your use of the Service by emailing at contact@adsy.com.

## 2\. HOW WE COLLECT THE INFORMATION

To facilitate your use of the Service, Adsy.com may automatically collect certain types of information when you access or use the Service, complete surveys, send and receive communications, perform search queries and marketing activities.

Adsy.com may use various technologies to collect and store information when you use our Services, and this may include using cookies and similar tracking technologies on our Website, such as pixels and web beacons, to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, serve targeted advertisements, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

2.1. Cookie Policies. “Cookies” are small text files which are transferred from our website, product or service and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use a combination of cookies to help us provide you with a personalised service, and also to help make our websites, products and services better for you. You are able to configure your browser to restrict or block cookies and similar technologies if you wish, however if you disable those you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website, products or services.

## 3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

3.1. Non-Personally Identifiable Information. We use non-personally identifiable information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to most common user needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

From time to time, we may use your information to contact you with details about our products and services which we feel may be of interest to you. We may also share your information with our group companies, business partners so that they (or we) can contact you with information about their products or services which we feel may be of interest to you.

3.2. Personally Identifiable Information. We use the personally identifiable user information that we collect to provide any information and services that you have requested or any products that you have ordered. We may also contact you for feedback on your use of our products, services or our website.

We may use and analyse the information that we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop the current Services offerings, to develop new Services, to be able to tailor the Services to one’s specific needs if feasible, for convenience of users and communication with them.

We may use that information to send you emails, invoices, receipts, notices of delinquency, and alerting you if we need a different credit card number or any information requested by our payment processors and gateways, including but not limited to PayPal, VISA, Mastercard, Amex, Discover, PayPro. We use third parties for secure credit card transaction processing, and we send billing information to those third parties to process your orders and credit card payments.

## 4\. DISCLOSURE

4.1. Disclosure to Third-Parties. Adsy.com does not share your personal information with third parties or the public except as set forth herein. We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers, such as SMTP infrastructure providers, analytical services, payment processors, merchants, or resellers, performing services, which supplement our Services. These service providers may have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions. Third parties with whom we share your data currently include, but are not limited to Google, OWOX, YouTube, Act-on, Sendgrid, Inspectlet, Adroll, Facebook and Twitter. We do not sell your personal information.

Adsy may also share your personal information with the partner third-parties, namely, GainRock. This information only includes your email and name you’ve specified on your account. We do not disclose your payment information. 

4.2. Research. We may use and disclose to third parties information we collect in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form for research and informational purposes and to help us make sales, marketing and business decisions.

4.3. Events and Webinars. Adsy.com may share the names, email addresses and other details of users who register for some of our webinars and events, both online and offline, with the respective webinar speakers, announced special guests, our partners at the events, and others. We carefully select these persons and require them to use this information for the purposes related to the event (including webinars). We will try to label such events (including webinars) on the registration forms therefor, but if you affirmatively do not wish your name, email address or other details disclosed, please contact us before registering for any Adsy.com event to confirm whether your personal information will be shared at the specific event that you are considering. You may not opt-out of sharing your information at an event where such information is shared. Your only recourse is not to register for an event which so shares information.

4.4. Mergers and Acquisitions. If Adsy.com is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to any new privacy policy of an acquirer of our business.

4.5. Special Circumstances. Adsy.com will not disclose your personally identifiable information except as set forth in this Section 4, including in subsections below:

  * when requested to do so by law enforcement agencies;
  * when obliged to do so under the law;
  * for the purpose of pursuing outstanding debts or liabilities;
  * and when given permission to do so by you.

4.6. Use of Information for Commercial Purposes. You may object to the use of your personal data for commercial purpose at any time by logging in to your Adsy account and managing your settings or by contacting us at contact@adsy.com.

## 5\. INFORMATION STORAGE

5.1. Permission to Use Information. By submitting your personal information, you agree to its transfer, storage or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We will store your usage data until such time when you withdraw your consent for us to do so. All other data as specified above will be retained for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may also retain information as required by law.

5.2. Password. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain Services or specific areas of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask that you do not share your password with anyone.

5.3. Disclaimer. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to us via the Internet; any such transmission is at your own risk.

## 6\. INFORMATION SECURITY

6.1. Security Measures. We protect your personal information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting, transferring, and handling sensitive data such as credit card information or personal data. SSL encryption is designed to make the information invisible to anyone but us. SSL encryption is enabled when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the top of your browser window. 

6.2. Limited Access to Information. We work hard to restrict access to personal information to Adsy.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

6.3. Be Aware. To prevent being a phishing website victim, always check domain details when you are providing your personal information. Please, be aware that if you suspect the website you are on is a fake site representing to be Adsy.com or to provide the Services, contact us directly at contact@adsy.com.

6.4. Controlling Your Personal Information. Adsy.com may, from time to time, make available to users chat rooms, forums, message boards, and other interactive features. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via blog, forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Adsy.com. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

6.5. Links. For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

6.6. Social media platforms and widgets. Our Websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. We also maintain presences on social media platforms including Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Reddit. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to us via a social media platform is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves. Your interactions with those features and platforms are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

## 7\. USERS’ RIGHTS

  * User has the right to amend and correct the provided data in a personal account;
  * User can change or delete his/her personal data in the user account;
  * User has the right to review his/her personal data and demand to transfer or delete this data;
  * User has the right to restrict collection and processing of data;
  * User is entitled to get his/her personal data anonymized.

## 8\. COMPLIANCE AND COOPERATION WITH REGULATORY AUTHORITIES

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self-regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

## 9\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to Adsy.com, through the Service, you represent that you are at least 16 years of age or older.

## 10\. TRANSFERS OUTSIDE EUROPE

Personal data in the European Union is protected by data protection laws but other countries do not necessarily protect your personal data in the same way. Our website and some of our products or services or parts of them may be hosted in the United States and this means that we may transfer any information which is submitted by you through the website, product or service outside the European Economic Area (which means all the EU countries plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein) (“EEA”) to the United States. When you send an email to us, this may also be stored on email servers which are hosted in the United States or outside the EU. We have taken steps to ensure that our hosting provider uses the necessary level of protection for your information but if you do not want your information to be transferred outside the EEA you should not use our website, product or service or contact us via email.

## 11\. NO ERROR-FREE PERFORMANCE

Adsy.com does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our reasonable efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

## 12\. DO NOT TRACK

Because there currently isn't an industry or legal standard for recognizing or honoring DNT (Do Not Track) signals, we don't respond to them at this time. We await the result of work by the privacy community and industry to determine when such a response is appropriate and what form it should take.

## 13\. LEGAL NOTICES

This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions, available for review at http://adsy.com/terms-and-conditions/. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

## 14\. CONTACT INFORMATION

Your privacy matters to Adsy.com so whether you are new to Adsy.com or a long time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices. Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to us by email at contact@adsy.com or to 2035 Sunset Lake Road, Suite B-2, Newark, DE, 19702.
